https://crystalharmonyfarms.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Inspired Theory
FREE SHIPPING ON ALL US ORDERS OVER $100!
Who we are
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Inspired Theory collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://www.crystalharmonyfarms.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Inspired Theory.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Information I Collect
To fulfil your order, you must provide me with certain information, such as your name, email address, postal address, payment information, and the details of the product that you’re ordering. You may also choose to provide me with additional personal information (for a custom piece of jewelry, for example), if you contact me directly.
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded Content from Other Websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
VIP Club
If you decide to opt-into our VIP Club, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. I may use third party service providers to help me operate my business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out VIP Club updates or surveys. I may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Why I Need Your Information and How I Use It
I rely on a number of legal bases to collect, use, and share your information, including:
As needed to provide my services, such as when I use your information to fulfil your order, to settle disputes, or to provide customer support;
When you have provided your affirmative consent, which you may revoke at any time, such as by signing up for my mailing list;
If necessary to comply with a legal obligation or court order or in connection with a legal claim, such as retaining information about your purchases if required by tax law; and
As necessary for the purpose of my legitimate interests, if those legitimate interests are not overridden by your rights or interests, such as providing and improving my services. I use your information to provide the services you requested and in my legitimate interest to improve my services.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
I do not sell, trade, or rent customers personal identification information to others.
Information about my customers is important to my business. I share your personal information for very limited reasons and in limited circumstances, as follows:
Service providers. I engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to my shop, such as delivery companies. I will share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these services.
Business transfers. If I sell or merge my business, I may disclose your information as part of that transaction, only to the extent permitted by law.
Compliance with laws. I may collect, use, retain, and share your information if I have a good faith belief that it is reasonably necessary to: (a) respond to legal process or to government requests; (b) enforce my agreements, terms and policies; (c) prevent, investigate, and address fraud and other illegal activity, security, or technical issues; or (d) protect the rights, property, and safety of my customers, or others.
How Long I Retain Your Data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
I retain your personal information only for as long as necessary to provide you with my services and as described in my Privacy Policy. However, I may also be required to retain this information to comply with my legal and regulatory obligations, to resolve disputes, and to enforce my agreements. I generally keep your data for the following time period: 4 years.
Transfers of Personal Information Outside the EU
I may store and process your information through third-party hosting services in the US and other jurisdictions. As a result, I may transfer your personal information to a jurisdiction with different data protection and government surveillance laws than your jurisdiction. If I am deemed to transfer information about you outside of the EU, I rely on Privacy Shield as the legal basis for the transfer, as Google Cloud is Privacy Shield certified.
What Rights You Have Over Your Data
If you reside in certain territories, including the EU, you have a number of rights in relation to your personal information. While some of these rights apply generally, certain rights apply only in certain limited cases. I describe these rights below:
Access. You may have the right to access and receive a copy of the personal information I hold about you by contacting me using the contact information below.
Change, restrict, delete. You may also have rights to change, restrict my use of, or delete your personal information. Absent exceptional circumstances (like where I am required to store data for legal reasons) I will generally delete your personal information upon request.
Object. You can object to (i) my processing of some of your information based on my legitimate interests and (ii) receiving marketing messages from me after providing your express consent to receive them. In such cases, I will delete your personal information unless I have compelling and legitimate grounds to continue using that information or if it is needed for legal reasons.
Complain. If you reside in the EU and wish to raise a concern about my use of your information (and without prejudice to any other rights you may have), you have the right to do so with your local data protection authority.
Where I Send Your Data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Contact Information
For purposes of EU data protection law, I, Susan Hass, am the data controller of your personal information. If you have any questions or concerns, you may contact me at sue@crystalharmonyfarms.com. Alternately, you may mail me at:
Susan Hass
2309 Sunset St NE
Mekinock, ND 58258
Additional Information
How I Protect Your Data
I adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
INFORMATIONMy Account
Sizing Guide
Wishlist
About
FAQs
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Home
Save 15% On Your First Order Become an Inspired Theory VIP to save 15% on your first order!  Plus you’ll get exclusive access to special sales, sneak peaks, and much more.  Sign up here.  I’ll never sell your information or spam you.
Let’s Connect!FacebookPinterestInstagram
© Inspired Theory
Necklaces
Bracelets
Earrings
Ankle Bracelets
Newest Items
Holds and Custom Orders
This is a demo store for testing purposes — no orders shall be fulfilled. Dismiss
